[{"answer": "Hi.  Can I help you", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 11, "question": "", "qSentId": 10},{"answer": "Im trying to make up my mind about what to get.  Everything in this case look", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 12, "question": "Hi.  Can I help you", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Yeah.  We have a lot of yummy things to choose from.  Just so you know", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 16, "question": "Im trying to make up my mind about what to get.  Everything in this case look", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " No wonder it all looks so good", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Yeah.  We have a lot of yummy things to choose from.  Just so you know", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": "We have cakes, brownies, cookies and pastries over here.  And we have bread", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 21, "question": " No wonder it all looks so good", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Actually, Im buying things for my girlfriends birthday party and she has a rea", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 25, "question": "We have cakes, brownies, cookies and pastries over here.  And we have bread", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " OK.  Well, we have a lot of sweet items here in this case", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Actually, Im buying things for my girlfriends birthday party and she has a rea", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": "This cake here looks good.  What kind is that", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 30, "question": " OK.  Well, we have a lot of sweet items here in this case", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": "Thats a vanilla cream cake", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 31, "question": "This cake here looks good.  What kind is that", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " That does look good, but she really likes chocolate.  Do you have any chocolat", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 35, "question": "Thats a vanilla cream cake", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Sure.  This is one of our most popular cakes.  Its a seven-layer chocolat", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 39, "question": " That does look good, but she really likes chocolate.  Do you have any chocolat", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Mmmm.  I bet she would like that.  How many people does it serve", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Sure.  This is one of our most popular cakes.  Its a seven-layer chocolat", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": "It serves between 10 and 12 people depending on how big you cut the slices", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Mmmm.  I bet she would like that.  How many people does it serve", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " OK.  Ill take one of those cakes please", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 45, "question": "It serves between 10 and 12 people depending on how big you cut the slices", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " OK.  Would you like anything else", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 46, "question": " OK.  Ill take one of those cakes please", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Yeah.  Id like to get a few more things.  What kind of cookies are these", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 47, "question": " OK.  Would you like anything else", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Those are double chocolate chip cookies", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Yeah.  Id like to get a few more things.  What kind of cookies are these", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Ooh.  Those sound good too.  Id like a dozen of those as well", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Those are double chocolate chip cookies", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Our cookies come in bakers dozens", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Ooh.  Those sound good too.  Id like a dozen of those as well", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " OK.  Thats fine.  Can I get a bakers dozen of the sugar cookies as well", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Our cookies come in bakers dozens", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Sure.  No problem.  Anything else", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 52, "question": " OK.  Thats fine.  Can I get a bakers dozen of the sugar cookies as well", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Let me get one more thing.  Can you recommend anything else thats popular", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Sure.  No problem.  Anything else", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Well, our pastries are very good and our brownies are a favorite with customer", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Let me get one more thing.  Can you recommend anything else thats popular", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " How much are the brownies", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 58, "question": " Well, our pastries are very good and our brownies are a favorite with customer", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Theyre $1 a piece", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 59, "question": " How much are the brownies", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " All right.  Let me get 10 brownies too, please", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Theyre $1 a piece", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Sure.  Would you like the cookies and brownies in the same box", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 61, "question": " All right.  Let me get 10 brownies too, please", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": "No.  If you could put them in separate boxes that would be great", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Sure.  Would you like the cookies and brownies in the same box", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " Sure.  No problem.  Would you like to buy some candles to go with the cake", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 63, "question": "No.  If you could put them in separate boxes that would be great", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " No thanks.  Ive got some at home already", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Sure.  No problem.  Would you like to buy some candles to go with the cake", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " All right.  Your total is going to be $45.62", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 68, "question": " No thanks.  Ive got some at home already", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " OK.  I have cash", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 69, "question": " All right.  Your total is going to be $45.62", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " OK.  Here you are.  Would you like a receipt", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 70, "question": " OK.  I have cash", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " No, thats OK.  Thank you", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 71, "question": " OK.  Here you are.  Would you like a receipt", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  Thanks for coming in", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 72, "question": " No, thats OK.  Thank you", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Sure.  Bye", "docId": "11-10", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Youre welcome.  Thanks for coming in", "qSentId": 72}]
